Guide to the Harry Randall: Fifteenth International Brigade Films and Photographs ALBA.PHOTO.011
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series A: Miscellaneous, August 1937-May 1938, 11281
  - Photo Unit #: A204 Damaged building, Teruel, Jan 1938; 11349 (Item 11-0873)
  - Photo Unit #: A212 MacKenzie-Papineau Battalion Machine-Gunner Company headquarters [in cave]; Makela, Teruel, Jan 1938; 11348 (Item 11-1249)
  - Photo Unit #: A214 MacKenzie-Papineau Battalion, Teruel [3 men with cooking pot], Jan 1938; 11347 (Item 11-1250)
  - Photo Unit #: A215 MacKenzie-Papineau Battalion, Teruel, Jan 1938; 11346 (Item 11-0874)
  - Photo Unit #: A217 MacKenzie-Papineau Battalion, Teruel, Jan 1938; 11345 (Item 11-1251)
  - Photo Unit #: A218 Pablo Carbonell, killed in action, MacKenzie-Papineau Battalion, Teruel, Jan 1938; 11344 (Item 11-0875)
  - Photo Unit #: A220 Bombardment, Teruel, Jan 1938; 11343 (Item 11-1252)
  - Photo Unit #: A222 Small farm building, explosions in the distance, 304901 (Item 11-1857)
  - Photo Unit #: A224 Estado Mayor "central" [Headquarters], Transmiciones [Transmissions], Teruel, Jan 1938; 11342 (Item 11-0876)
  - Photo Unit #: A225 MacKenzie-Papineau positions, Seguro de Los Baños, Feb 1938; 11341 (Item 11-0877)
  - Photo Unit #: A228 Estado Mayor [Headquarters], Seguro de Los Baños, Feb 1938; 11340 (Item 11-0878)
  - Photo Unit #: A230 MacKenzie-Papineau, [3 men in] trench, Teruel, Jan 1938; 11339 (Item 11-1253)
    Available Formats: Print
    (Moscow Number: 5/187/28)
  - Photo Unit #: A241 MacKenzie-Papineau, [2 men in] trenches, Seguro de Los Baños, Feb 1938; 11338 (Item 11-1254)
  - Photo Unit #: A242 MacKenzie-Papineau trenches, Seguro de Los Baños [torn and damaged print], Feb 1938; 11337 (Item 11-1255)
  - Photo Unit #: A243 MacKenzie-Papineau trenches, Seguro de Los Baños, Feb 1938; 11336 (Item 11-1256)
    Available Formats: Original Negative; Print; Moscow negative
    (Moscow Number: 5/187/11)
  - Photo Unit #: A245 First aid in MacKenzie-Papineau trench, Seguro de Los Baños, Feb 1938; 11335 (Item 11-1257)
    (Moscow Number: 5/187/10)
  - Photo Unit #: A246 Mackenzie-Papineau [soldier] in trench with sighting device, 304902 (Item 11-1858)
  - Photo Unit #: A249 MacKenzie-Papineau positions, Seguro de Los Baños, Feb 1938; 11334 (Item 11-0589)
  - Photo Unit #: A250 MacKenzie-Papineau positions, Seguro de Los Baños, Feb 1938; 11333 (Item 11-0590)
    (Moscow Number: 5/187/18)
  - Photo Unit #: A251 Two Mackenzie-Papineau soldiers in trench, 304903 (Item 11-1859)
  - Photo Unit #: A254 Mackenzie-Papineau soldiers in trench fortification, 304904 (Item 11-1860)
  - Photo Unit #: A255 MacKenzie-Papineau positions, Feb 1938; 11332 (Item 11-1258)
  - Photo Unit #: A256 MacKenzie-Papineau positions, Seguro de Los Baños, Feb 1938; 11331 (Item 11-0591)
  - Photo Unit #: A258 MacKenzie-Papineau positions, Seguro de Los Baños, [working on a machine gun], Feb 1938; 11330 (Item 11-1763)
    (Moscow Number: 5/180/54)
  - Photo Unit #: A259 MacKenzie-Papineau position, Seguro de Los Baños, Feb 1938; 11329 (Item 11-1829)
    (Moscow Number: 5/187/5)
  - Photo Unit #: A262 MacKenzie-Papineau Battalion after Seguro de Los Baños, [two soldiers with a machine gun], Feb 1938; 11328 (Item 11-1837)
    (Moscow Number: 5/187/26)
  - Photo Unit #: A267 MacKenzie-Papineau positions, Seguro de Los Baños, Feb 1938; 11327 (Item 11-0592)
  - Photo Unit #: A268 MacKenzie-Papineau soldier in trench firing rifle, 304905 (Item 11-1861)
  - Photo Unit #: A269 MacKenzie-Papineau positions, Seguro de Los Baños [2 men in trench], Feb 1938; 11326 (Item 11-1259)
  - Photo Unit #: A270 MacKenzie-Papineau positions, Seguro de Los Baños, Feb 1938; 11325 (Item 11-0593)
    (Moscow Number: 5/187/37)
  - Photo Unit #: A271 MacKenzie-Papineau positions, Seguro de Los Baños, Feb 1938; 11324 (Item 11-0594)
  - Photo Unit #: A274 View from MacKenzie-Papineau trenches, Seguro de Los Baños, Feb 1938; 11323 (Item 11-0595)
  - Photo Unit #: A279 MacKenzie-Papineau positions, Teruel, Jan 1938; 11322 (Item 11-0879)
  - Photo Unit #: A280 MacKenzie-Papineau positions, Teruel, Jan 1938; 11321 (Item 11-1260)
  - Photo Unit #: A281 American Artillery unit emplacement, Teruel front, Feb 1938; 11320 (Item 11-0880)
  - Photo Unit #: A283 American Artillery unit emplacement, Teruel front, Feb 1938; 11319 (Item 11-0881)
  - Photo Unit #: A284 American Artillery unit emplacement, Teruel front, Feb 1938; 11318 (Item 11-0882)
  - Photo Unit #: A286 American Artillery unit emplacement, Teruel front [copy negative; transferred from the Victor Berch Papers, ALBA 080], Jan 1938; 369366 (Item 11-1884)
  - Photo Unit #: A289 British Battalion on maneuvers, Mondejar, Dec 1937; 11317 (Item 11-0883)
  - Photo Unit #: A290 Fascist posters on the square, Belchite, Sep 1937; 11316 (Item 11-0596)
  - Photo Unit #: A291 Street scene, Belchite, Aug 1937; 11315 (Item 11-0597)
  - Photo Unit #: A292 Street scene, Belchite, Aug 1937; 11314 (Item 11-0598)
  - Photo Unit #: A294 MacKenzie-Papineau group poses for the camera, 304920 (Item 11-1862)
  - Photo Unit #: A295 MacKenzie-Papineau Transmiciones [Transmissions]: William (Red) Brown and [?], Teruel, Jan 1938; 11313 (Item 11-0884)
  - Photo Unit #: A296 Lincoln-Washington front lines, Teruel, Jan 1938; 11312 (Item 11-0885)
  - Photo Unit #: A300 British Battalion Machine-Gunner nest, Teruel, Jan 1938; 11311 (Item 11-0886)
  - Photo Unit #: A301 British Battalion, Company crew machine-gun nest, Teruel, Jan 1938; 11310 (Item 11-1261)
  - Photo Unit #: A306 Transmiciones [Transmissions] repairing Estado Mayor [Headquarters] telephone, Valeverde, Mar 1938; 11309 (Item 11-0887)
  - Photo Unit #: A313 Group at Estado Mayor [Headquarters], Teruel, Jan 1938; 11308 (Item 11-0888)
  - Photo Unit #: A316 Engineers working on dugouts (Hiyar), Mar 1938; 11307 (Item 11-1764)
    (Moscow Number: 5/180/66)
  - Photo Unit #: A317 Observers, Aragon Retreat, Marcelina Marot and Harvey Hall, Lebux, Mar 1938; 11306 (Item 11-1262)
  - Photo Unit #: A318 Engineers building refugios, Lebux, Mar 1938; 11305 (Item 11-0889)
  - Photo Unit #: A320 MacKenzie-Papineau trenches [?], Seguro de Los Baños [view over fields to factories in distance], undated; 11304 (Item 11-1263)
  - Photo Unit #: A321 MacKenzie-Papineau trenches, Teruel, Jan 1938; 11303 (Item 11-1264)
  - Photo Unit #: A323 MacKenzie-Papineau trenches, Ebro Front, undated; 11302 (Item 11-1265)
  - Photo Unit #: A324 MacKenzie-Papineau trenches, Ebro Front, May 1938; 11301 (Item 11-0599)
  - Photo Unit #: A326 15th International Brigade troops marching, Mollerusa, May 1938; 11300 (Item 11-0890)
  - Photo Unit #: A328 Dr. Mark Straus, May 1938; 11299 (Item 11-0115)
  - Photo Unit #: A330 Panorama, Codo [with church and houses], Aug 1937; 11298 (Item 11-1266)
  - Photo Unit #: A332 Our artillery firing at Belchite, Sep 1937; 11297 (Item 11-1267)
  - Photo Unit #: A335 Five soldiers loading artillery, Belchite[?], 304921 (Item 11-1863)
  - Photo Unit #: A337 During the battle, Belchite, Sep 1937; 11296 (Item 11-1268)
  - Photo Unit #: A338 During the battle, Belchite, Sep 1937; 11295 (Item 11-1269)
  - Photo Unit #: A339 Church during the battle, Belchite [with carts in foreground], Sep 1937; 11294 (Item 11-1270)
  - Photo Unit #: A340 Church in Belchite [ruined interior], Sep 1937; 11293 (Item 11-1271)
  - Photo Unit #: A342 Machine-Gunner crew, British Battalion, Tarraga, May 1938; 11292 (Item 11-1272)
  - Photo Unit #: A343 Machine-Gunner crew, British Battalion, Tarraga [in tall grass], May 1938; 11291 (Item 11-1273)
    (Moscow Number: 5/187/34)
  - Photo Unit #: A344 MacKenzie-Papineau Transmiciones [Transmissions], Tarraga, May 1938; 11290 (Item 11-0891)
  - Photo Unit #: A346 Troops of 15th International Brigade on march, Tarraga, May 1938; 11289 (Item 11-0892)
  - Photo Unit #: A348 15th International Brigade troops on march, Tarraga, May 1938; 11288 (Item 11-1274)
  - Photo Unit #: A350 Aviation, Tarraga, May 1938; 11287 (Item 11-0893)
  - Photo Unit #: A352 MacKenzie-Papineau Battalion, Transmiciones [Signal Corps], heliographer, undated; 11286 (Item 11-1845)
    (Moscow Number: 5/187/44)
  - Photo Unit #: A353 MacKenzie-Papineau Battalion Heliographer, Tarraga, May 1938; 11285 (Item 11-0894)
  - Photo Unit #: A354 Transmissions, Tarraga, May 1938; 11284 (Item 11-0895)
  - Photo Unit #: A355 Armorer at work (Harry Farris), Tarraga, May 1938; 11283 (Item 11-0896)
  - Photo Unit #: A356 Machine-Gunners on trip from Albacete to Barcelona, Tarraga, Apr 1938; 11282 (Item 11-0600)
  - Photo Unit #: A357 Two soldiers with machine gun, 304922 (Item 11-1864)
- Series B: Individual Portraits, September 1937-September 1938, 10865
  Series IIB: Individual Portraits, September 1937 - September 1938. The Unit photographers had hoped to photograph every member the 15th Brigade. Although this formidable task was never realized, the 415 portraits in this series depict prominent members of the Brigade including Political Commissars Joseph Dallet, John Robinson, Saul Wellman, George Watt, Archie Brown, and Chief of the Brigade Commissariat Sandor Voros. Portraits of other Brigade members include Chief of Brigade Staff Robert Merriman, Commander Milton Wolff, Commander 15th Brigade Vladimir Copic, Dr. Mark Straus, Volunteer for Liberty editor John Tisa, and writers Alvah Bessie and Edwin Rolfe. This series also includes portraits of Photo Unit photographers Ben Katine and Harry Randall.
  - Photo Unit #: B001 Carl Bradley, former commander of American Company, 24th Battalion, Sep 1937; 11280 (Item 11-0601)
  - Photo Unit #: B002 Wally Sabatini, Political Commissar, Company 3, MacKenzie-Papineau, Sep 1937; 11279 (Item 11-0602)
  - Photo Unit #: B003 Carl Bradley, Sep 1937; 11278 (Item 11-0603)
  - Photo Unit #: B004 John Robinson, Adjutant Political Commissar, 15th International Brigade, Sep 1937; 11277 (Item 11-0604)
  - Photo Unit #: B005 Wilton Chite, Lincoln-Washington Battalion, from Musicians Union #802, Sep 1937; 11276 (Item 11-0605)
  - Photo Unit #: B006 William Newton Miller, Sep 1937; 11275 (Item 11-0606)
  - Photo Unit #: B007 Owen Appleton, Battalion Secretary, Lincoln-Washington, killed at Fuentes de Ebro, Oct 1937; 11274 (Item 11-0607)
  - Photo Unit #: B008 Philip Detro, Battalion Commander, Lincoln-Washington, Nov 1937; 11273 (Item 11-0116)
  - Photo Unit #: B009 Vete Zablackas, Transmiciones [Transmissions], Sep 1937; 11272 (Item 11-0608)
  - Photo Unit #: B010 Corporal Louis Zivin, Lincoln-Washington Sanidad [Health], Sep 1937; 11271 (Item 11-0609)
  - Photo Unit #: B011 Dimitri Semenoff, Lincoln-Washington (Yugoslav), Sep 1937; 11270 (Item 11-0610)
  - Photo Unit #: B012 Sergeant [?] Mowbray, Lincoln-Washington Sanidad [Health], Sep 1937; 11269 (Item 11-0611)
  - Photo Unit #: B013 Elkan Wendkos, Machine-Gunner Company, Lincoln-Washington, Sep 1937; 11268 (Item 11-0612)
  - Photo Unit #: B014 Moe [?] Fishman, Transmiciones [Transmissions], Sep 1937; 11267 (Item 11-0613)
  - Photo Unit #: B016 Radomir Smrcka, Chief of Information, Sep 1937; 11266 (Item 11-0614)
  - Photo Unit #: B017 James Bourne, Sep 1937; 11265 (Item 11-0615)
  - Photo Unit #: B018 [?] Aguila, 24th Battalion Commander, Sep 1937; 11264 (Item 11-0616)
  - Photo Unit #: B021 Thomas MacNulty, Company 1, Lincoln-Washington, Sep 1937; 11263 (Item 11-0617)
  - Photo Unit #: B022 Peter Nielson, Company 1, Lincoln-Washington, Sep 1937; 11262 (Item 11-0618)
  - Photo Unit #: B023 Kenneth Brown, Company 1, Lincoln-Washington, Sep 1937; 11261 (Item 11-0619)
  - Photo Unit #: B024 Dimitri Semenoff, Company 1, Lincoln-Washington, Sep 1937; 11260 (Item 11-0620)
  - Photo Unit #: B025 Dimitri Semenoff, Company 1, Lincoln-Washington, Sep 1937; 11259 (Item 11-0621)
  - Photo Unit #: B026 Lionel Levick, Lincoln-Washington Battalion, Company 1, Sep 1937; 11258 (Item 11-1275)
  - Photo Unit #: B027 John Petrullo, Company 1, Lincoln-Washington, Sep 1937; 11257 (Item 11-0622)
  - Photo Unit #: B029 Leon [Leo?] Markowitz, 15th International Brigade Commissariat, Dec 1937; 11256 (Item 11-1276)
  - Photo Unit #: B030 Ely Sack, MacKenzie-Papineau Battalion, Dec 1937; 11255 (Item 11-0897)
  - Photo Unit #: B034 Paddy O'Dair, British Battalion, Nov 1937; 11254 (Item 11-1277)
  - Photo Unit #: B036 Donald Thayer, Lincoln-Washington Battalion Staff, Sep 1937; 11253 (Item 11-0623)
  - Photo Unit #: B037 Owen Appleton, Lincoln-Washington Battalion Secretary, Sep 1937; 11252 (Item 11-0624)
  - Photo Unit #: B038 Douglas Hitchcock, MacKenzie-Papineau Battalion Secretary, Sep 1937; 11251 (Item 11-0625)
  - Photo Unit #: B039 Jack Kramer, Transmiciones [Transmissions] driver, Sep 1937; 11250 (Item 11-0626)
  - Photo Unit #: B040 Ivan Rujevcic, Military Intelligence Service, Sep 1937; 11249 (Item 11-0627)
    (Moscow Number: 5/188/12)
  - Photo Unit #: B044 Joseph Sands, food truck, Lincoln-Washington, Oct 1937; 11248 (Item 11-0628)
  - Photo Unit #: B045 Joseph Dallet, Political Commissar, MacKenzie-Papineau, Oct 1937; 11247 (Item 11-0629)
    (Moscow Number: 5/187/7)
  - Photo Unit #: B046 Alfred Chakin, MacKenzie-Papineau quartermaster, Oct 1937; 11246 (Item 11-0630)
  - Photo Unit #: B047 Milton Wolff, Adjuntant of Lincoln-Washington Battalion, Dec 1937; 11245 (Item 11-0631)
  - Photo Unit #: B048 George Kay, Lincoln-Washington, Dec 1937; 11244 (Item 11-0632)
  - Photo Unit #: B055 Ralph Thorton, filing clerk in Commissariat, Dec 1937; 11243 (Item 11-0633)
  - Photo Unit #: B056 Major Robert Merriman, Chief of Brigade Staff, Dec 1937; 11242 (Item 11-0634)
  - Photo Unit #: B057 Major Robert Merriman, Chief of Brigade Staff, Dec 1937; 11241 (Item 11-0635)
  - Photo Unit #: B058 Major Robert Merriman, Chief of Brigade staff, Dec 1937; 11240 (Item 11-1278)
    (Moscow Number: 5/177/12)
  - Photo Unit #: B059 Captain Rollin Dart, Brigade Staff, Dec 1937; 11239 (Item 11-0636)
  - Photo Unit #: B060 Captain Rollin Dart, Brigade Staff, Dec 1937; 11238 (Item 11-0637)
  - Photo Unit #: B061 John Hunter, Lincoln-Washington Machine-Gunner Company 1, Dec 1937; 11237 (Item 11-0638)
  - Photo Unit #: B063 John Hunter, Lincoln-Washington Machine-Gunner Company 1, Dec 1937; 11236 (Item 11-0639)
  - Photo Unit #: B065 Captain Robert Thompson, Battalion Commander, MacKenzie-Papineau, Dec 1937; 11235 (Item 11-0117)
  - Photo Unit #: B066 Captain Robert Thompson, MacKenzie-Papineau Battalion, Nov 1937; 11234 (Item 11-1841)
    (Moscow Number: 5/187/36)
  - Photo Unit #: B067 Louis Secundy, Chief of Auto Park, Dec 1937; 11233 (Item 11-1279)
  - Photo Unit #: B068 Louis Secundy, Chief of Auto Park, Dec 1937; 11232 (Item 11-0640)
  - Photo Unit #: B069 Joseph Dion, Lincoln-Washington Machine-Gunner, Nov 1937; 11231 (Item 11-0641)
  - Photo Unit #: B070 [?] Anderson, Danish Seaman, Lincoln-Washington Battalion, Nov 1937; 11230 (Item 11-0642)
  - Photo Unit #: B071 Hans Kaltschmidt, Adjuntant to Chief of Brigade, Sep 1937; 11229 (Item 11-0643)
  - Photo Unit #: B072 Nathan Weisenfeld, Chief of Brigade Runners, Nov 1937; 11228 (Item 11-0898)
  - Photo Unit #: B073 Elhanon Winchester Bridges, Company 3, Lincoln-Washington Battalion, Nov 1937; 11227 (Item 11-0899)
  - Photo Unit #: B074 Milton Gale, Estado Mayor [Headquarters], Political Commissar, Nov 1937; 11226 (Item 11-0900)
  - Photo Unit #: B076 James Bourne, Nov 1937; 11225 (Item 11-0644)
  - Photo Unit #: B077 John Robinson, Nov 1937; 11224 (Item 11-0645)
  - Photo Unit #: B078 Paul White, Nov 1937; 11223 (Item 11-0646)
  - Photo Unit #: B080 Sid Rosenthall [?], Lincoln-Washington Battalion Clerk, Nov 1937; 11222 (Item 11-0647)
  - Photo Unit #: B082 Vincent Sanchis, Adjuntant of Company 3, MacKenzie-Papineau Battalion, Nov 1937; 11221 (Item 11-0901)
  - Photo Unit #: B083 Samuel Willis, MacKenzie-Papineau Scout, Nov 1937; 11220 (Item 11-1280)
  - Photo Unit #: B084 Nulo Makela, undated; 11219 (Item 11-1281)
  - Photo Unit #: B086 Thoman Mallon, Political Commissar, Machine-Gunner Company, MacKenzie-Papineau, Nov 1937; 11218 (Item 11-0902)
  - Photo Unit #: B087 Eugene Nolte, MacKenzie-Papineau Battalion Secretary, Nov 1937; 11217 (Item 11-0903)
  - Photo Unit #: B088 James Craddock, MacKenzie-Papineau Chief of Staff, Nov 1937; 11216 (Item 11-0648)
  - Photo Unit #: B089 Claude Pringle, MacKenzie-Papineau souper, Nov 1937; 11215 (Item 11-0904)
  - Photo Unit #: B090 Thomas Norton from Reed College, Portland, Oregon, Nov 1937; 11214 (Item 11-0649)
  - Photo Unit #: B095 James Cox, Lincoln-Washington Battalion, Nov 1937; 11213 (Item 11-0650)
  - Photo Unit #: B096 Irving Halpern, Brigade motorcyclist, Nov 1937; 11212 (Item 11-1282)
    Available Formats: Original Negative; Print
  - Photo Unit #: B097 Major [?] Crespo, Brigade Staff, Nov 1937; 11211 (Item 11-0651)
  - Photo Unit #: B098 Lieutenant Harry Poll [Pollitt?], Nov 1937; 11210 (Item 11-0652)
  - Photo Unit #: B099 Albert Chisholm, artist for Brigade Bulletin, Nov 1937; 11209 (Item 11-0653)
  - Photo Unit #: B100 Larry Dukes, Nov 1937; 11208 (Item 11-0654)
  - Photo Unit #: B101 Edward Bender, Nov 1937; 11207 (Item 11-0655)
  - Photo Unit #: B102 George Kaye, Nov 1937; 11206 (Item 11-0656)
  - Photo Unit #: B103 Robert Thompson, Captain, MacKenzie-Papineau, Nov 1937; 11205 (Item 11-1283)
  - Photo Unit #: B104 Pat Barcena [Isador (Frank) Barcena?], Transmiciones [Transmissions], Nov 1937; 11204 (Item 11-0001)
  - Photo Unit #: B106 Jacob Kramer, Transmiciones [Transmissions] driver, Nov 1937; 11203 (Item 11-0002)
  - Photo Unit #: B110 Ernest Kozlowski, brigade scout, Nov 1937; 11202 (Item 11-0905)
  - Photo Unit #: B111 Arthur Landis, MacKenzie-Papineau topographer, Nov 1937; 11201 (Item 11-0003)
  - Photo Unit #: B114 David Gordon of Brigade Commissariat, Dec 1937; 11200 (Item 11-0906)
  - Photo Unit #: B115 David Gordon of Brigade Commissariat, Dec 1937; 11199 (Item 11-0907)
  - Photo Unit #: B116 Emiliano Marin, Cuban in Lincoln-Washington Battalion, Dec 1937; 11198 (Item 11-0657)
  - Photo Unit #: B117 Thain Summers, officers training school, Nov 1937; 11197 (Item 11-0658)
  - Photo Unit #: B118 Joseph Taylor, Brigade scout, Dec 1937; 11196 (Item 11-0659)
  - Photo Unit #: B119 Albert Chisholm, artist on commissariat staff, Nov 1937; 11195 (Item 11-0660)
  - Photo Unit #: B120 Captain Philip Detro, Chief, Lincoln-Washington Battalion, Nov 1937; 11194 (Item 11-1284)
  - Photo Unit #: B121 [?] Rosenstein, one of the original Lincoln Boys, Nov 1937; 11193 (Item 11-0661)
  - Photo Unit #: B122 Benjamin Katine, 15th International Brigade photographer, Dec 1937; 11192 (Item 11-0908)
  - Photo Unit #: B123 Benjamin Katine, 15th International Brigade photographer, Dec 1937; 11191 (Item 11-0909)
  - Photo Unit #: B124 Jack Mullinger, Chief of Scouts, Dec 1937; 11190 (Item 11-0910)
    (Moscow Number: 5/188/89)
  - Photo Unit #: B126 Michael Pavlos, chief cook in Estado Mayor [Headquarters] kitchen, Dec 1937; 11189 (Item 11-0911)
  - Photo Unit #: B127 William Oderaka, Lab. Assistant in Photo Department, Dec 1937; 11188 (Item 11-0912)
  - Photo Unit #: B128 William Buchkowski, Political Commissar of Brigade Scouts, Dec 1937; 11187 (Item 11-0913)
  - Photo Unit #: B132 Charles Kersh, driver in Auto Park, Dec 1937; 11186 (Item 11-0914)
  - Photo Unit #: B133 [?] Gallinat of Transmiciones [Transmissions], Dec 1937; 11185 (Item 11-0915)
  - Photo Unit #: B134 Max Farrar, cook in Estado Mayor [Headquarters] kitchen, Dec 1937; 11184 (Item 11-0916)
  - Photo Unit #: B135 Albert Harris, 15th International Brigade Intendencia, Dec 1937; 11183 (Item 11-0917)
  - Photo Unit #: B136 William Frame, Intendencia, Dec 1937; 11182 (Item 11-0662)
  - Photo Unit #: B137 Fredrick Lutz, Political Commissar, Intendencia, Dec 1937; 11181 (Item 11-0663)
  - Photo Unit #: B138 Thomas O'Malley, Intendencia, Dec 1937; 11180 (Item 11-0664)
  - Photo Unit #: B140 Dr. Luis Diaz Soto, Lincoln-Washington medical staff, Dec 1937; 11179 (Item 11-0665)
  - Photo Unit #: B141 Dr. Luis Diaz Soto, Lincoln-Washington medical staff, Dec 1937; 11178 (Item 11-0666)
  - Photo Unit #: B143 Arthur Landis of MacKenzie-Papineau at Brigade Mapping School, Dec 1937; 11177 (Item 11-0004)
  - Photo Unit #: B144 Dionesio Aleman (Cuban), Chief, Company 2, 24th Battalion, Dec 1937; 11176 (Item 11-0918)
  - Photo Unit #: B145 Angel Garcia of MacKenzie-Papineau Battalion, Dec 1937; 11175 (Item 11-0919)
  - Photo Unit #: B146 Harry Schoenberg, MacKenzie-Papineau Battalion, Dec 1937; 11174 (Item 11-1285)
  - Photo Unit #: B147 Edward Cecil Smith, Captain of MacKenzie-Papineau Battalion, Dec 1937; 11173 (Item 11-1286)
  - Photo Unit #: B148 Joseph Kaplan, MacKenzie-Papineau Battalion, Dec 1937; 11172 (Item 11-0920)
  - Photo Unit #: B151 José María Varela, 15th International Brigade Commissar, Dec 1937; 11171 (Item 11-1287)
  - Photo Unit #: B157 Enrique Santana Torregroso, Sergeant, 24th Battalion, distinguished, Dec 1937; 11170 (Item 11-0921)
  - Photo Unit #: B169 John Givulinovich, MacKenzie-Papineau Battalion, Dec 1937; 11169 (Item 11-0922)
  - Photo Unit #: B170 Frank Migone Flores, Political Commissariat Member, Dec 1937; 11168 (Item 11-0923)
  - Photo Unit #: B171 Bert Jackson, mapper for Brigade, Dec 1937; 11167 (Item 11-0667)
  - Photo Unit #: B173 Manuel [?] Dong Hong Yick, Lincoln-Washington Battalion, Dec 1937; 11166 (Item 11-0924)
  - Photo Unit #: B175 John William Snyder [?], Cabo, Lincoln-Washington Battalion, Dec 1937; 11165 (Item 11-0925)
  - Photo Unit #: B176 Horace Kark, Cabo, Lincoln-Washington Battalion, Dec 1937; 11164 (Item 11-0926)
  - Photo Unit #: B177 Lawrence Kleidman, Cabo, Lincoln-Washington Battalion, Dec 1937; 11163 (Item 11-1290)
  - Photo Unit #: B178 Charles Kuchs [?], driver, Auto Park, Dec 1937; 11162 (Item 11-0927)
  - Photo Unit #: B179 [Benjamin] Butch Goldstein, Cabo, MacKenzie-Papineau Battalion, Dec 1937; 11161 (Item 11-1291)
  - Photo Unit #: B180 John Washington, Cabo, MacKenzie-Papineau Battalion, Dec 1937; 11160 (Item 11-0928)
  - Photo Unit #: B184 Wally Tapsell, undated; 11159 (Item 11-1292)
  - Photo Unit #: B188 John [?] Hunter (or Oscar Hunter), Dec 1937; 11158 (Item 11-0929)
  - Photo Unit #: B190 Sergeant Elliot Loomis (Transmiciones [Transmissions]), Dec 1937; 11157 (Item 11-0930)
  - Photo Unit #: B193 Sidney Bassin, 15th Brigade Auto Park Chauffeur, Dec 1937; 11156 (Item 11-0931)
  - Photo Unit #: B196 Sergeant Harry W. Randall, Jr. Brigade Photographer, Dec 1937; 11155 (Item 11-0932)
  - Photo Unit #: B197 Milford Chapin (Blackie, "Idaho"), MacKenzie-Papineau cook, Dec 1937; 11154 (Item 11-0933)
  - Photo Unit #: B198 Walter "Kid" O'Kane, (Transmiciones [Transmissions]), Dec 1937; 11153 (Item 11-0934)
  - Photo Unit #: B199 Wilfred Cowan, Dec 1937; 11152 (Item 11-0935)
  - Photo Unit #: B200 John Givulinovich [alias John Givins], MacKenzie-Papineau Battalion Intendencia, Dec 1937; 11151 (Item 11-0936)
  - Photo Unit #: B201 Salman Salzman (Palestine), MacKenzie-Papineau, Battalion, Dec 1937; 11150 (Item 11-0937)
  - Photo Unit #: B202 Captain Alfredo Balsa, Dec 1937; 11149 (Item 11-1293)
  - Photo Unit #: B203 Paddy Stafford, British anti-tank battery, Dec 1937; 11148 (Item 11-0938)
  - Photo Unit #: B204 Lieutenant Colonel Vladimir Copic, Commander, 15th International Brigade, Dec 1937; 11147 (Item 11-0939)
  - Photo Unit #: B208 Fred Keller, Political Commissar, Lincoln-Washington Battalion, Dec 1937; 11146 (Item 11-0940)
  - Photo Unit #: B209 Ben Kasinap, first aid man in Transmiciones [Transmissions], Dec 1937; 11145 (Item 11-0668)
  - Photo Unit #: B212 Argente, Jan 1938; 11144 (Item 11-0941)
  - Photo Unit #: B213 Abraham Lewis at Argente, Jan 1938; 11143 (Item 11-0942)
  - Photo Unit #: B215 Milton Gale, Jan 1938; 11142 (Item 11-0943)
  - Photo Unit #: B216 Lieutenant William Digges, Jan 1938; 11141 (Item 11-0944)
    (Moscow Number: 5/188/88)
  - Photo Unit #: B221 Raul Rojas (Cuban), Spanish Battalion, Jan 1938; 11140 (Item 11-0945)